{
    "question": "Soal Ujian Semester Genap    SMAN 3 KARANG BARU\r\nTP. 2020-2021\r\nMata Pelajaran\r\nNama\r\n: Bahasa Inggris Peminatan\r\n: Minarti, S.Pd\r\nKelas/Jurusan :X MIA IIS\r\nHari/Tanggal :\r\nPilihlah salah satu jawaban yang paling tepat!\r\nCHOOSE THE CORRECT ANSWER!\r\nThe following text is for number 1 to 8\r\nGalileo Galilei (1564-1642) \u2014 Astronomer and Scientist. Galileo developed a superior telescope and made\r\nmany significant discoveries in astronomy. He was sentenced to life imprisonment by the inquisition for his\r\nsupport for the Copernican theory that the sun was at the centre of the solar system.\r\nGalileo was born in Florence, Italy in 1564 to a poor but noble family His parents recognized their child's\r\ninnate intelligence and talents and so made sacrifices to have him educated. At his father's insistence, Galileo\r\nstudied the profitable career of medicine. But, at the University of Pisa, Galileo became fascinated in a wide\r\nrange of subjects. He was also critical of many of Aristotle's teaching which had dominated education for the\r\npast 2,000 years.\r\nGalileo was appointed to be a mathematics professor at the University of Pisa, but his strident criticisms of\r\nAristotle left him isolated among his contemporaries. After three years of persecution, he resigned and went\r\nthe University of Padua, where he taught maths. His entertaining lectures attracted a large following and he\r\nable to spend the next 18 years pursuing his interests in astronomy and mechanics.\r\n1. What type of the text above?\r\nA. Narrative.\r\nB. Report.\r\nBiography\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Narrative </p><p>Teks Me-narasikan Kehidupan Galileo Galilei Dari Tahun 1564-1642, dan Penemuannya Serta Galileo Galilei yang berakhir di penjara. CMIIW</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Semoga Membantu</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "do-you-know-what-the-cars-the-beatles-330",
            "question": "Do you know what the cars The Beatles\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Yeah I Know karena aku pernah mendengarnya</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>I Know I Know karena aku pernah melihat ulasannya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-do-you-man-you-stupid-bahasakan-indonesia-dengan-benar-jan-406",
            "question": "What do you man you stupid\r\n Bahasakan indonesia dengan benar!! Jangan ngasal ok.....",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>What do you man you stupid</p><p>kalau di translate kan ke Indonesia:</p><p>Apa yang kamu lakukan, kamu bodoh </p><p></p><p>Kalau ga salah,kalau salah HAPUS aja gpp kok(\u2500.\u2500||\uff09</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>What do you man, you stupid</p><p> adalah sebuah pengucapan mengejek dalam bahasa inggris. Apa arti dari kata bahasa inggris tersebut jika dittransletkan ke bahasa indonesia?</p><p>Artinya adalah</p><p>= Apa yang kamu lakukan, kamu bodoh</p><p>Pengartian ini juga sudah terdeteksi oleh translate.</p><p>Terimakasih, semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "di-musim-kemarau-cuacanya-adingin-bberkabut-cberawan-dberangi-891",
            "question": "Di musim kemarau cuacanya a.dingin b.berkabut c.berawan d.berangin\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>b. berkabut</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>karena tidak ada hujan</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C. berawan</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jack-used-to-amerika-993",
            "question": "Jack used to ...... Amerika\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>go</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>yyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy</p><p>apa</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "3-they-arrive-in-my-house-last-night-and-4-study-an-english-l-351",
            "question": "3. They arrive) in my house last night and    4. study) an english last week i studied\r\n5. My father (buy) a car in Jakarta ( bought\r\n122\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>3. Arrived</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p><strong>Menggunakan simple past tense</strong></p><p><strong>rumusnya (+) S+V2</strong></p><p>nomor 4 dan 5 sudah ada jawabannnya</p><p>4. studied</p><p>5. bought</p><p>Smoga membantu maaf klo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "roni-what-is-time-is-it-jodi-it-is-jika-jarum-panjang-di-angk-119",
            "question": "Roni : what is time is it    Jodi : it is \r\n\r\nJika jarum panjang di angkat 11 dan jarum pendek di angkat 12 jadi jam berapa ya kak \r\n\r\nTolong di jawab",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>11.55 am / 23.55 pm</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>tergantung siang (am) atau malam (pm)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>11.45 am</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p><p><strong>se</strong><strong>moga</strong><strong> membantu</strong><strong>,</strong><strong> maaf</strong><strong> kalo</strong><strong> salah</strong><strong>,</strong><strong> jangan</strong><strong> lupa</strong><strong> jadikan</strong><strong> jawaban</strong><strong> terbaik</strong><strong> yah</strong><strong>.</strong><strong>.</strong></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p><strong>answe</strong><strong>r</strong><strong> </strong><strong>by</strong><strong> </strong><strong>:</strong><strong> </strong><strong>sendah379</strong></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p><strong>#</strong><strong>m</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>k</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>s</strong><strong>i</strong><strong>h</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "5-dang-dao-tubis-sian-932",
            "question": "5. Dang dao tubis sian\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>arti dari kata - kata bahasa batak &#039; ndang dao tubis sian bonana &#039; memiliki arti yakni sebagai berikut : </p><p></p><p>Secara harafiah : </p><p>Tidaklah jauh rebung dari pokok bambu.</p><p>Artinya : </p><p>Tingkah laku atau perangai seorang anak , tidak akan jauh dari tingkah laku atau tidak akan jauh dari perangai ayahnya</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu dan maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "0-rearrange-these-random-letters-into-a-good-word-a-r-u-s-m-e-m-786",
            "question": "0. Rearrange these random letters into a good word    a r-u-s-m-e-m\r\nb. w-e-n-r-i-t\r\nAnswer:\r\n\r\ntolong di jawab kak\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a. Summer</p><p>b. Winter</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Semoga Membantu!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a. summer</p><p>b. winter</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "hamish-and-his-friends-went-snorkeling-at-the-563",
            "question": "Hamish and his friends went snorkeling at the ....",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Hamish and his friends went snorkeling at the <u>sea</u></p><p><strong></strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kata-kerja-present-perfect-tense-dari-bring-hate-feat-finish-238",
            "question": "Kata kerja present perfect tense dari= bring, hate, feat, finish, di, draw, kick, write, call",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>arti dari kata tersebut adalah= bawa, benci, prestasi, selesaikan, di, gambar, tendang, tulis, panggil</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga bermanfaat</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}